Guide to the Trade catalogs collection.
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Trade catalogs collection.
1800-1978
Uai Trade Catalogs
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
125.0
(8174 volumes)
Trade catalogs collected by Yale University Library.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred from Sterling Memorial Library.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Scope and Contents
The Trade Catalogs collection consists of over 8,000 printed items varying in size from small pamphlets to multipart volumes that date from the early 19th century to the mid-20th century. The manufacturing companies represented in the collection are primarily American, the bulk being from New England and the Mid-Atlantic; a small number of Western European companies are also included. The catalogs list products ranging from domestic wares to industrial equipment and often include prices and illustrations; some catalogs also contain information about the manufacturers.
Information in this finding aid was taken from catalog cards. The catalog cards have been retained and are found in box 406. The primary set of cards is arranged alphabetically by manufacturer's name. A secondary set of duplicate cards for Connecticut manufacturers are found at the end of the primary set. These materials were given the Yale classification: Uai.
The collection was transferred to Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library from Sterling Memorial Library.
Arrangement
Arranged alphabetically by manufacturer's name.
Manufacturing industries -- Catalogs; Manufactures -- Catalogs; Commercial catalogs -- Specimens.; Trade catalogs
- A
  - Abbey and Imbrie (New York, N.Y.), undated; 1 volume (Box 399, Folder 4287)
    Scope and Contents
    Fishing tackle
  - Abbey and Imbrie, Division of Wright and Ditson (New York, N.Y.), 1930; Uai Ab19; 1 volume (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Abbott Laboratories (North Chicago, Ill., etc.), 1938–1941; Uai +Ab29; 5 volumes (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Vitamin charts, etc.
  - Abrasive Material Company (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1896–1923; Uai +Ab84; 4 volumes (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Grinding wheels
  - Acetol Products, Inc. (New York, N.Y.), 1931; Uai +Ac36; 1 volume (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Cel-o-glass, Glass substitutes
  - Ackroyd and Best, Ltd. (Morley, England), 1923; Uai +Ac58; 1 volume (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Glassware
  - Acme Card System Company (Chicago, Ill.), 1927–1928; Uai +Ac64; 2 volumes (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Visible records
  - Acme Equipment Co., Inc. (Chicago, Ill.), 1949; Uai +Ac643; 1 volume (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Acme Manufacturing Company (Reading, Pa.), 1897–1900; Uai Ac645; 2 volumes (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Stormer and "Pennant" bicycles
  - Acme Stationary and Paper Co. (Brooklyn, N.Y.), 1896–1897; Uai +Ac65; 4 volumes (Box 1, Folder 9)
    School paper and stationary
  - Acme Wire Co. (New Haven, Conn.), 1936; Uai Ac67; 2 volumes (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Acme coil windings, Magnet wire standards
  - Adam, Frank, Electric Company (St. Louis, Mo.), 1925; Uai +Ad12; 1 volume (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Panelboards, Steel cabinets
  - Adamant Plaster Company (New York, N.Y.), undated; Uai Ad13; 1 volume (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Wall plaster
  - Adams and Jones (Boston, Mass.), 1897; Uai +Ad17; 1 volume (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Ideal boilers
  - Adams and Jones Westlake Company (Chicago, Ill.), 1899; Uai +Ad19; 3 volumes (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Adlake bicycles, Adlake automobile system
  - Addressograph Company (London, England), 1901–1928; Uai +Ad28; 2 volumes (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Addressing machines
  - Adjustable Drawing Table Co. (Grand Rapids, Mich.), undated; Uai Ad49; 1 volume (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Drawing tables
  - Adnet, E., et Fils, (Paris, France), 1912; Uai Ad68; 2 volumes (Box 5, Folder 221-222)
    Laboratory utensils
  - Adt, John (New Haven, Conn.), 1882; Uai +Ad88; 1 volume (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Machinery for hardware manufacturers
  - Adt, John and Son (New Haven, Conn.), 1884–1889; Uai +Ad89; 9 volumes (Box 1, Folder 18)
    Machinery
  - Aero Fire Alarm Company (New York, N.Y.), 1913; Uai Ae82; 3 volumes (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Fire alarm systems
  - Aero Pulverizer Company (New York, N.Y.), 1907; Uai Ae83; 2 volumes (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Pulverizer fuel machinery
  - Aerovox Wireless Corporation (Brooklyn, N.Y.), 1928–1931; Uai +Ae84; 2 volumes (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Condensers and resistors
  - Agfa Ansco Corporation (Binghamton, N.Y.), 1937; Uai +Ag37; 2 volumes (Box 13)
    Photographic supplies
  - Agostino, Valerio, 1885; Uai Ag75; 1 volume (Box 1, Folder 22)
    Bulbs, seeds, and plants
  - Air Reduction Company, Inc. (New York, N.Y.), 1941; Uai +Ai68; 1 volume (Box 1, Folder 23)
    Manufacturing tools, etc.
  - Airola Corporation (Essex, Conn.), 1941; Uai Ai7; 1 volume (Box 1, Folder 24)
    Airola humidifier
  - Ajax Electric Company, Inc. (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1938; Uai +Aj2; 2 volumes (Box 1, Folder 25)
    Furnaces
  - Aktien-Gesellschaft für Anilin-Fabrikation (Berlin, Germany), 1902; Uai Ak75; 1 volume (Box 1, Folder 26)
    Agfa photographic supplies
  - Aktiengesellschaft für Klepper-Sporterzeugnisse (Zurich, Switzerland), 1933–1938; Uai Ak79; 2 volumes (Box 1, Folder 27)
    Sports clothes, etc.
  - Aladdin Company (Bay City, Mich.), 1919–1921; Uai AL1; 2 volumes (Box 1, Folder 28-29)
    Aladdin homes
  - Aladdin Electric Company (Ravenna, Ohio), undated; Uai AL11; 1 volume (Box 1, Folder 30)
    Refilled lamps
  - Alba Pharmaceutical Company, Inc. (New York, N.Y.), 1941; Uai AL13; 1 volume (Box 1, Folder 31)
    Stramid
  - Alberene Stone Company (New York, N.Y.), undated; Uai AL139; 1 volume (Box 1, Folder 32)
    Laundry tubs
  - Alberger Pump and Condenser Company (New York, N.Y.), 1906–1913; Uai +AL14; 3 volumes (Box 1, Folder 33)
    Wainwright, Heaters
  - Albi Chemical Corporation (New York, N.Y.), 1942; Uai +AL149; 1 volume (Box 13)
    Firepel fire retardant
  - Alden Products Company (Brockton, Mass.), 1944; Uai +AL221; 1 volume (Box 1, Folder 34)
    Facsimile, Radio components
  - Alexander, Andrew (New York, N.Y.), 1900–1901; Uai +AL26; 1 volume (Box 1, Folder 35)
    Men's shoes
  - Alfred Clay Company (Alfred, N.Y.), 1899; Uai +AL29; 1 volume (Box 1, Folder 36)
    Roof tiles
  - Allegheny Ludlum Steel Corporation (Pittsburgh, Pa.), undated; Uai AL5; 1 volume (Box 1, Folder 37)
    Allegheny stainless steel, etc.
  - Allegheny Steel Company (Brackenridge, Pa.), 1934; Uai +AL51; 2 volumes (Box 1, Folder 38)
    Allegheny metal
  - Allen Paper Car Wheel Company (New York, N.Y.), 1881; Uai +AL543; 1 volume (Box 1, Folder 41)
    Car wheels
  - Allen, W.D., Manufacturing Company (Chicago, Ill.), 1911; Uai +AL54; 4 volumes (Box 1, Folder 40)
    Hose brass goods
  - Allen, William A., and Company (New York, N.Y.), 1933; Uai +AL53; 1 volume (Box 1, Folder 39)
    Novelties, Gift wares
  - Allen-Bradley Company (Milwaukee, Wis.), 1926–1927; Uai +AL542; 1 volume (Box 6, Folder 223)
    Electric controlling apparatus
  - Allied Chemical and Dye Corporation (New York, N.Y.), 1944–1945; Uai +AL549; 2 volumes (Box 1, Folder 42)
    Dealear's price list
  - Allied Machinery Company of America (New York, N.Y.), 1911–1932; Uai +AL55; 1 volume (Box 1, Folder 43)
    Grinding machines
  - Allied Radio Corporation (Chicago, Ill.), 1929–1952; Uai AL56; 6 volumes (Box 1, Folder 44-47)
    Radios, Home electronics, etc.
  - Alling's, George, Sons' Company (New Haven, Conn.), 1894; Uai +AL571; 1 volume (Box 1, Folder 48)
    Moldings
  - Allis-Chalmers Company (Milwaukee, Wis.), 1903–1909; Uai +AL58; 2 volumes (Box 1, Folder 49)
    Hydraulic turbines
  - Aloe, A.S., Company (St. Louis, Mo.), 1910; Uai AL71; 1 volume (Box 1, Folder 50)
    Engineering instruments, Drawing materials
  - Alpha Portland Cement Company (Easton, Pa.), 1917–1919; Uai +AL73; 12 volumes (Box 1, Folder 51-54)
    Concrete
  - Alpine Wax Oil Polish Company (New York, N.Y.), 1909–1910; Uai AL75; 3 volumes (Box 1, Folder 55)
    Wood polish
  - Alsen's Portland Cement Works (Itzehoe, Germany), 1883; Uai +AL78; 1 volume (Box 1, Folder 56)
    Portland cement
  - Altmann, Paul (Berlin, Germany), undated; Uai +AL81; 1 volume (Box 1, Folder 57)
    Chemical apparatus
  - Aluminum Company of America (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1929; Uai +AL82; 1 volume (Box 1, Folder 58)
    Aluminum shingles
  - Alvergniat Frères (Paris, France), 1873; Uai +AL87; 1 volume (Box 1, Folder 59)
    Chemical and physiological instruments
  - Amberg File and Index Company (New York, N.Y.), 1897; Uai +Am16; 2 volumes (Box 1, Folder 60)
    Filing cabinets
  - American Iron and Steel Manufacturing Company (Lebanon, Pa.), 1903–1907; Uai Am3416; 5 volumes (Box 2, Folder 94)
    Bolts, rivets, screws
  - America Metal Hose Company (Waterbury, Conn.), 1930; Uai +Am3451; 1 volume (Box 2, Folder 102)
    Flexible metal hose
  - American Aristotype Company (Jamestown, N.Y.), undated; Uai +Am33; 1 volume (Box 1, Folder 61)
    Self-toning paper
  - American Art Works, Inc. (Coshocton, Ohio), 1931; Uai Am3311; 1 volume (Box 1, Folder 62)
    Gifts
  - American Ball Company (Providence, R.I.), 1903; Uai Am3321; 2 volumes (Box 1, Folder 63)
    Ball bearings
  - American Bicycle Company (New York, N.Y., etc.), 1900–1902; Uai +Am3323; 8 volumes (Box 1, Folder 64)
    Bicycles
  - American Blower Corporation (Detroit, Mich.), 1930; Uai Am3324; 2 volumes (Box 1, Folder 65)
    Ventilating units
  - American Brake Company (St. Louis, Mo.), 1885–1900; Uai +Am3326; 2 volumes (Box 7, Folder 224-225)
    Automobile brakes
  - American Brass Company (Ansonia, Conn.), 1921–1938; Uai +Am3327; 8 volumes (Box 2, Folder 66-68)
    Copper tubing and pipes
  - American Brass and Metal Works (Detroit, Mich.), 1892; Uai +Am3328; 1 volume (Box 2, Folder 69)
    Railings, grills, and wire work
  - American Car and Foundry Company (New York, N.Y.), 1927; Uai Am3331; 1 volume (Box 2, Folder 70)
    Storm and steel or freight cars
  - American Carbonate Company (New York, N.Y.), 1887; Uai +Am3332; 1 volume (Box 2, Folder 71)
    Compressed gas
  - American Cement Company (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1892; Uai +Am3333; 1 volume (Box 2, Folder 72)
    Portland cement industry
  - American Chain Company (Bridgeport, Conn.), 1912–1923; Uai +Am3334; 6 volumes (Box 2, Folder 73-75)
    Chains
  - American Clothes Dryer Company (New York, N.Y.), 1913; Uai Am3337; 2 volumes (Box 2, Folder 76)
    Clothes dryers
  - American Compound Telegraph Wire Company (Boston, Mass.), 1868; Uai +Am3339; 1 volume (Box 2, Folder 77)
    Telegraph wire
  - American Cotton Company (New York, N.Y.), 1902–1904; Uai Am3341; 2 volumes (Box 2, Folder 78)
    Cotton bailing machinery
  - American Cyanamid Company (New York, N.Y., etc.), 1934–1945; Uai Am3343; 5 volumes (Box 15)
    Dyes, etc.
  - American Cycle Manufacturing Company (New York, N.Y., etc.), 1902–1903; Uai +Am3344; 4 volumes (Box 389)
  - American Desk and Stool Company (New York, N.Y.), undated; Uai Am3348; 1 volume (Box 2, Folder 79)
    Desks
  - American Diamond Rock-Boring Company (Providence, R.I.) and Pennsylvania Diamond Drill Company (Pottsville, Pa.), 1876; Uai +Am33486; 1 volume (Box 2, Folder 80)
    Diamond drill
  - American Electric Switch Company (Springfield, Mass.), undated; Uai Am3356; 1 volume (Box 2, Folder 81)
    Switches
  - American Enamel Decorating Company (New Haven, Conn.), 1874; Uai +Am3359; 1 volume (Box 2, Folder 82)
    Ceramic ware decorating
  - American Flask and Cap Company (Waterbury, Conn.), 1864; Uai +Am3368; 1 volume (Box 2, Folder 83)
    Powder flasks and caps
  - American Fomon Company (Philadelphia. Pa.), 1927; Uai +Am3371; 1 volume (Box 2, Folder 84)
    Fomon fire extinguishing chemicals
  - American Forestry Company (Boston, Mass.), undated; Uai +Am3542; 1 volume (Box 3, Folder 125)
    Tree farms
  - American Forestry Company (Boston, Mass., South Framingham Mass.), 1910–1917; Uai +Am3372; 2 volumes (Box 2, Folder 85)
    Little tree farms
  - American Gas Furnace Company (New York, N.Y.), 1907–1914; Uai +Am3377; 6 volumes (Box 2, Folder 86-88)
    Fuel plants, Blast furnaces
  - American Gas Machine Company, Inc. (Albert Lea, Minn.), 1930; Uai Am33776; 1 volume (Box 2, Folder 89)
    Cooking, heating, and lighting appliances
  - American Gas Products Corporation, Division of American Radiator and Standard Sanitary Corporation (New York, N.Y.), 1931–1933; Uai +Am3378; 11 volumes (Box 2, Folder 90)
    House and water heating equipment
  - American Hardware Corporation (New Britain, Conn.), 1911–1920; Uai +Am338; 4 volumes (Box 8, Folder 226-227)
    "Corbin" coaster brakes, "Russwin" hardware, etc.
  - American Hoist and Derrick Company (St. Paul, Minn.), 1915–1916; Uai Am3394; 4 volumes (Box 2, Folder 91)
    Crosby clipper
  - American Instrument Company (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1907; Uai +Am3413; 1 volume (Box 2, Folder 92)
    Electrical measuring instruments
  - American Insulating Material Manufacturing Company (St. Louis, Mo.), 1907; Uai +Am3414; 1 volume (Box 2, Folder 93)
    Insulating materials
  - American Jobbers Supply Company (New York, N.Y., etc.), 1925; Uai +Am342; 1 volume (Box 9, Folder 228)
    Electrical equipment, Construction materials
  - American Laundry Machinery Company (Kenilworth, N.J.), 1937; Uai +Am3437; 1 volume (Box 2, Folder 96)
    Rebuilt laundry machines
  - American Lead Pencil Company (New York, N.Y.), 1929; Uai Am3439; 2 volumes (Box 2, Folder 97)
    Venus pencils
  - American Luxfer Prism Company (New York, N.Y.), 1912; Uai +Am3444; 3 volumes (Box 2, Folder 98)
    Prism windows, Skylights, etc.
  - American Machine and Foundry Company (New Haven, Conn.), 1938; Uai Am34445; 1 volume (Box 2, Folder 99)
    Crawford industrial ovens
  - American Machine and Metals Manufacturing Corporation (East Moline, Ill.), 1937; Uai +Am34447; 1 volume (Box 2, Folder 100)
    Laundry machinery
  - American Manufacturing Company (New York, N.Y.), 1902–1905; Uai +Am3447; 2 volumes (Box 2, Folder 101)
    Rope transmission
  - American Monorail Company (Cleveland, Ohio), 1935; Uai +Am3455; 1 volume (Box 2, Folder 103)
    Overhead conveyors
  - American Needle and Fish Hook Company (New Haven, Conn.), 1885; Uai +Am3462; 3 volumes (Box 2, Folder 104)
    Fishing hooks
  - American Nokol Company (Chicago, Ill.), 1923; Uai Am3466; 2 volumes (Box 2, Folder 105)
    Nokol oil burners
  - American Optical Company (Southbridge, Mass.), 1912–1946; Uai +Am347; 4 volumes (Box 10, Folder 229-231)
    Optical goods
  - American Phenolic Corporation (Chicago, Ill.), 1942; Uai +Am3481; 1 volume (Box 2, Folder 106)
    Radio, electrical, and aeronautical products
  - American Pneumatic Service Company (Boston, Mass.), 1906–1914; Uai Am3485; 3 volumes (Box 2, Folder 107-108)
    Lawson conveyors
  - American Pulley Company (New York, Chicago, etc.), 1915; Uai +Am349; 2 volumes (Box 2, Folder 109)
    Steel reels, beams, pulleys, etc.
  - American Radiator Company (New York, N.Y.), 1900–1911; Uai +Am3511; 5 volumes (Box 2, Folder 110-111)
    Radiators and boilers
  - American Ring Company (Waterbury, Conn.), 1923; Uai +Am3513; 1 volume (Box 2, Folder 112)
    Brass furniture trimmings
  - American Road Machine Company (Kennett Square, Pa.), 1887; Uai +Am3515; 1 volume (Box 2, Folder 113)
    Road graders
  - American Rolling Mill Company (Middletown, Ohio), 1931; Uai Am3517; 1 volume (Box 2, Folder 114)
    Sheet iron and steel
  - American Ru-Mari Company (Los Angeles, Cal.), 1936–1937; Uai Am352; 2 volumes (Box 2, Folder 115)
    "Ru-mari" ["ro-mari"], Arthritis medication
  - American Sales Company (New York, N.Y.), 1932; Uai +Am3522; 2 volumes (Box 3, Folder 116-117)
    Radio supplies
  - American Sash and Door Company (Kansas City, Mo.), 1916; Uai +Am3523; 1 volume (Box 14)
    Fixtures, mantels, doors, etc.
  - American Screw Company (Providence, R.I.), 1936; Uai +Am3528; 1 volume (Box 3, Folder 119)
    Screws, bolts, etc.
  - American Seating Company (Chicago, Ill.), 1919; Uai Am3527; 1 volume (Box 3, Folder 118)
    School furniture and supplies
  - American Sewer Pipe Company (Akron, Ohio), 1912; Uai +Am3529; 2 volumes (Box 3, Folder 120)
    Sewer pipes
  - American Spiral Pipe Works (Chicago, Ill.), 1901–1908; Uai +Am3535; 3 volumes (Box 3, Folder 121-122)
    Riveted pipe
  - American Steam Pump Company (Battle Creek, Mich.), 1913–1921; Uai +Am3538; 2 volumes (Box 3, Folder 123)
    Pumping machinery
  - American Steel and Wire Company (Chicago, Ill., Cleveland, Ohio), 1932–1949; Uai +Am3541; 15 volumes (Box 11, Folder 232-236)
    Springs, wire rope, etc.
  - American Sterilizer Company (Erie, Pa.), 1935–1937; Uai +Am35414; 1 volume (Box 3, Folder 124)
    Sterilizers, etc.
  - American Stove Company (St. Louis, Mo.), 1929; Uai +Am35423; 1 volume (Box 16)
    "Magic Chef" stoves
  - American Swiss File and Tool Company (New York, N.Y.), 1912; Uai Am3544; 1 volume (Box 3, Folder 126)
    Swiss files
  - American Tap and Die Company (Greenfield, Mass.), 1909; Uai Am3545; 1 volume (Box 3, Folder 127)
    Adamantine tools
  - American Telephone and Telegraph Company, undated; 1 volume (Box 399, Folder 4288)
    Bell systems
  - American Thermos Bottle Company (Norwich, Conn.), 1914; Uai +Am355; 1 volume (Box 3, Folder 128)
    "Thermos" products
  - American Tool Works (Cincinnati, Ohio), 1931; Uai Am3551; 1 volume (Box 3, Folder 130)
    New plant
  - American Tool and Machine Company (Boston, Mass.), 1944–1946; Uai Am355o; 1 volume (Box 3, Folder 129)
    Wester hydro-extractors
  - American Transformer Company, 1946; Uai Am3552; 1 volume (Box 3, Folder 131)
    Transformers
  - American Vulcanized Fibre Company (Wilmington, Del.), 1909; Uai Am3554; 1 volume (Box 3, Folder 132)
    Vulcanized fiber parts
  - American Well Works (Aurora, Ill.), undated; 2 volumes (Box 399, Folder 4289)
    Pumps
  - American Wheelman and Cycle Trade (New York, N.Y., etc.), 1894; 1 volume (Box 400)
    Bicycles, etc.
  - American Wire Brush Company (New York, N.Y.), 1923; Uai Am3574; 1 volume (Box 3, Folder 133)
    Wire brushes
  - American Wood Fire-Proofing Company, Ltd. (New York, N.Y.), 1943; Uai Am3575; 1 volume (Box 3, Folder 134)
    Fire-proofed wood
  - American Wood Working Machinery Company (Rochester, N.Y.), 1924; Uai +Am3576; 1 volume (Box 3, Folder 135)
    Wood working machinery
  - American Woolen Company (Boston, Mass.), 1910; Uai +Am3577; 1 volume (Box 3, Folder 136)
    "American Woolen Company" properties
  - American Writing Paper Company, Inc. (Holyoke, Mass.), 1940; Uai +Am358; 1 volume (Box 3, Folder 137)
    Eagle-A Coupon Bond paper
  - American Writing Paper Company, Inc. (Holyoke, Mass.), undated; Uai Am3579; 1 volume (Box 3, Folder 138)
    Coupon bond
  - American-La France Fire Engine Company (Elmira, N.Y.), undated; Uai +Am3435; 1 volume (Box 2, Folder 95)
    Firefighting equipment
  - Ames Iron Works, Division of Pierce, Butler, and Pierce Manufacturing Corporation (Oswego, N.Y.), 1925–1926; Uai +Am37; 3 volumes (Box 3, Folder 141)
    Engines and boilers
  - Ames Plow Company (Boston, Mass.), 1900; Uai +Am38; 1 volume (Box 3, Folder 142)
    Farming and contractors' equipment
  - Ames, B.C., Company (Waltham, Mass.), 1913–1930; Uai +Am36; 3 volumes (Box 3, Folder 139-140)
    Dial gauges
  - Ams, Max Machine Company (Bridgeport, Conn.), undated; Uai Am83; 1 volume (Box 3, Folder 143)
    Seam closing machine parts list
  - Amsler, C.T. (Philadelphia, P.A.), 1860; Uai Am84; 1 volume (Box 3, Folder 144)
    Mathematical, optical, and philosophical instruments
  - Amsterdam, Inc. (New York, N.Y.), 1923; Uai +Am88; 1 volume (Box 3, Folder 145)
    "Amsterdam" women's wear
  - Anaconda Wire and Cable Company (New York, N.Y.), 1936–1949; Uai +An13; 11 volumes (Box 12, Folder 237-240)
    Building wire, Service cables, etc.
  - Anchor Post Company (New York, N.Y.), undated; Uai An21; 4 volumes (Box 3, Folder 146)
    "Anchor" fence post
  - Anchor Post Iron Works (New York, N.Y.), 1906–1922; Uai +An211; 7 volumes (Box 3, Folder 147-148)
    Posts and fencing
  - Andernach, A.W. in Beuel a. Rhein, undated; Uai An22; 1 volume (Box 3, Folder 149)
    Asphalt paper
  - Anderson, Albert and J.M. Manufacturing Company (Boston, Mass.), 1933; Uai +An229; 7 volumes (Box 3, Folder 150-152)
    Connectors, plugs, switches, and receptacles
  - Andrae, Julius, and Sons Company (Milwaukee, Wis.), 1897–1898; Uai An25; 2 volumes (Box 3, Folder 153)
  - Andrews, A.H., Company (Chicago, Ill.), 1887–1906; Uai +An26; 3 volumes (Box 3, Folder 154)
    Office furniture
  - Andrews-Demarest Seating Company (New York, N.Y.), 1892–1894; Uai +An28; 3 volumes (Box 3, Folder 155)
    Desks and chairs
  - Angelica Jacket Company (St. Louis, Mo., New York, N.Y., etc.), 1935–1942; Uai +An43; 8 volumes (Box 3, Folder 156-158)
    Uniforms for domestic service, hospitals, hotels, etc.
  - Anheuser-Busch (St. Louis, Mo.), 1931; Uai +An49; 1 volume (Box 3, Folder 159)
    Malt products
  - Ansley Radio Corporation (New York, N.Y.), 1937; Uai An81; 1 volume (Box 3, Folder 160)
    Ansley dynaphone
  - Ansonia Manufacturing Company (Ansonia, Conn., New York, N.Y.), 1926; Uai An85; 1 volume (Box 3, Folder 161)
    Sewage ejectors
  - Anthony, E. and H. J. and Company (New York, N.Y.), 1860–1911; Uai +An86; 6 volumes (Box 3, Folder 162-163)
    Stereoscopic views, Photographic materials, Lantern views
  - Apfel-Murdoch Company (Chicago, Ill.), undated; Uai +Ap27; 2 volumes (Box 3, Folder 164)
    Chemists' apparatus and supplies
  - Apothecaries Hall Company (Waterbury, Conn.), 1931–1941; Uai +Ap47; 2 volumes (Box 3, Folder 165)
    Drugs, Spray materials, Fertilizers, etc.
  - Appleseed, Johnny (Beverly, Mass.), undated; Uai Ap52; 1 volume (Box 3, Folder 166)
    Household goods
  - Appleton Electric Company (Chicago, Ill.), 1919; Uai +Ap54; 1 volume (Box 3, Folder 167)
    Lamps, Light bulbs, etc.
  - Architectural Iron Works (New York, N.Y.), 1902; Uai +Ar25; 1 volume (Box 17)
    Iron architecture
  - Architectural Iron Works of the City of New York (New York, N.Y.), 1865; Uai +Ar26; 1 volume (Box 18)
  - Arlington Chemical Company (Yonkers, N.Y.), 1907–1912; Uai Ar5; 4 volumes (Box 3, Folder 168)
    "Liquid peptonoids"
  - Arlington Company (New York, N.Y.), undated; Uai +Ar51; 1 volume (Box 3, Folder 169)
    Pyralin enamels
  - Armour Fertilizer Works, Department of Armour and Company (Chicago, Ill.), 1896; Uai +Ar55; 1 volume (Box 4, Folder 172)
    Fertilizers
  - Armour and Company (Chicago, Ill.), 1917–1939; Uai +Ar54; 6 volumes (Box 4, Folder 170-171)
    Meat-packing, Vitamins, "Suprarenalin"
  - Armstrong Brothers Tool Company (Chicago, Ill.), 1920; Uai Ar561; 2 volumes (Box 4, Folder 174)
    Tool holders
  - Armstrong Cork Company (Lancaster, Pa.), 1917–1933; Uai +Ar568; 4 volumes (Box 4, Folder 175)
    Linoleum, etc.
  - Armstrong Cork Products Company (Lancaster, Pa.), 1917–1937; Uai +Ar57; 48 volumes (Box 4, Folder 177-181)
  - Armstrong Cork and Insulation Company (Lancaster, Pa.), 1917–1931; Uai +Ar569; 2 volumes (Box 4, Folder 176)
    Building insulation, Noise reduction, etc.
  - Armstrong Machine Works (Three Rivers, Mich.), 1931; Uai Ar571; 2 volumes (Box 4, Folder 182)
    Steam traps
  - Armstrong, E.A., Manufacturing Company (Chicago, Ill.), 1905; Uai +Ar56; 1 volume (Box 4, Folder 173)
    Cadet uniforms
  - Army and Navy Co-operative Company (New York, N.Y.), 1916; Uai +Ar59; 1 volume (Box 4, Folder 183)
    U.S. Army uniforms
  - Arnold-Roberts Company (Boston, Mass.), 1941; Uai +Ar64; 2 volumes (Box 4, Folder 184)
    Paper
  - Arnstein, Eugene (Chicago, Ill.), 1900; Uai +Ar66; 1 volume (Box 4, Folder 185)
    Bicycle supplies
  - Arrow Aircraft and Motors Corporation (Havelock, Nebr.), 1943; Uai +Ar67; 1 volume (Box 4, Folder 186)
    Airplane
  - Arrow Electric Company (Hartford, Conn.), 1913–1923; Uai Ar68; 3 volumes (Box 4, Folder 187)
    Wiring specialties